<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>print on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</title>
    <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/print/</link>
    <description>Recent content in print on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/print/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fireside Follies</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/fireside-follies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/fireside-follies/</guid>
      <description>Fireside Follies is a monthly reading series based out of Bushwick, New York, featuring the best up and coming literature to be found anywhere.
I illustrated and designed the posters for this project in its beginning stages, incorporating new elements into the illustrations, such as music, as the event grew. It’s a beautiful thing.
For more information on Fireside Follies, take a look at the official website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>in: The Conde Nast Intern Magazine</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/intern-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/intern-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Participants in the Condé Nast Summer Internship Program have the opportunity of taking part in an intern-produced, created, and published magazine which is distributed internally at the end of the summer. Put together entirely outside of our internships, this magazine required a great deal of teamwork and coordination to pull together in the short ten weeks we had, several of which were dedicated to planning.
As Art Director, I worked with the Creative Director in implementing a consistent visual theme throughout the magazine, designing several spreads and tweaking others to give the magazine a cohesive look and feel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roberto Cavalli Milestone Promotion</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/roberto-cavalli-milestone/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/roberto-cavalli-milestone/</guid>
      <description>I created this two-sided promotional sheet during my time as an intern at Women’s Wear Daily for a special milestone section celebrating Roberto Cavalli’s 40th anniversary.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
