<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>editorial on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/editorial/</link><description>Recent content in editorial on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 20:11:28 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/editorial/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Good Life of Marcia Deihl</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/designing-marcia-deihl/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2016 20:11:28 -0500</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/designing-marcia-deihl/</guid><description>&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->
&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s been a while since something I&amp;rsquo;ve done has gotten personal.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You know the feeling - when something is important, and it&amp;rsquo;s &lt;em>really&lt;/em> important, but it&amp;rsquo;s not even just important to you. It&amp;rsquo;s important to everyone.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Every Cell Has a Story</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/neil-ganem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/neil-ganem/</guid><description>I was lucky enough to be able to work with the amazing Joe Chan on this one. After I read this article, one thing stuck out at me, and it stuck out hard: how much dedication do you have to have to look at cells dividing for days on end? I really wanted to capture that and make it the centerpiece of the article.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever sat down, and done something, and then looked up and it&amp;rsquo;s suddenly hours later, you know what I mean when I say you do something like this, and time is different for you.</description></item><item><title>Africa Research Series</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/africa-research-series/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/africa-research-series/</guid><description>This three-part series gives an in-depth look at three Boston University researchers studying African culture. I used hand-drawn traditional patterns and colors to help capture the unique feel of each area while maintaining a unifying element across the series.
After the writer, Susan Seligson, described the stories to me and her own personal experiences while visiting Africa, the first thing I wanted to know was what the language sounded like. Lesotho: Life on the Edge offered a perfect opportunity to bring that into the design.</description></item><item><title>Dubious DNA</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/dubious-dna/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/dubious-dna/</guid><description>The heart of this piece focuses on a researcher who is working to improve the reliability of DNA profiling for crime scenes, and throughout the article, she calls into question the many factors that may cause incorrect profiling - leading to the grim possibility an innocent person could be convicted. In my design, I let these questions hang in the air uncomfortably around the crime scenes they inhabit, like the dust, skin cells, and flecks they raise concerns about.</description></item><item><title>High Notes</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/high-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/high-notes/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It's a Date, I Think</title><link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/its-a-date/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/its-a-date/</guid><description>Selected for inclusion in the 49thPublication Design Annual, published by the Society of Publication Designers</description></item></channel></rss>