<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>professional speaking &amp; writing on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</title>
    <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/professional-speaking-writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in professional speaking &amp; writing on Portfolio | Ashley Kolodziej - Boston Freelance Web Designer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.lastletterdesign.com/categories/professional-speaking-writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Prototyping, reflection, and identity: Unusual applications of the WordPress REST API</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/prototyping-reflection-identity-unusual-applications-wordpress-rest-api/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/prototyping-reflection-identity-unusual-applications-wordpress-rest-api/</guid>
      <description>Speaking at LoopConf was an incredible (and terrifying) opportunity. Going up to that podium as someone who knows just enough PHP to get by - and speaking about my experiences to a room full of the smartest WordPress developers out there - is something I&amp;rsquo;ll always be grateful for. But I&amp;rsquo;ll never forget the feeling of having K. Adam White introduce himself to me and say how much my talk meant to him.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I do(n&#39;t) belong here</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/imposter-syndrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/imposter-syndrome/</guid>
      <description>From the teaser:
Have you been faking it this whole time? Yeah, me too. In this session we’re going to have a heart to heart about what it’s like to experience imposter syndrome and what leads us to put unending pressure on ourselves to achieve. We’ll talk about growing up, entering the workforce and the challenges imposters face in their careers.
And if you’re not an imposter, that’s okay too, because we’ll also talk about ways to create environments that encourage everyone to contribute and take risks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating meaningful editorial experiences with the WordPress REST API</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/wp-rest-api-in-editorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/wp-rest-api-in-editorial/</guid>
      <description>See the post on Link: The Journal of Higher Education Web Professionals</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Just Build It: Seven Years of Framework Development at Boston University</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/lets-just-build-it-seven-years-framework-development-boston-university/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/lets-just-build-it-seven-years-framework-development-boston-university/</guid>
      <description>From the teaser:
The inside look at how the four most terrifying words ever uttered in development history have worked out for Boston University. We’ll cover seven years of successes and lessons learned in framework development, including enforcing brand guidelines in the site, when to allow customization and when to say no, and how on earth to make one codebase flexible enough to accommodate the requests we foresee – and the ones we don’t.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WordPress in Higher Education Panel</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/wordpress-in-higher-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/wordpress-in-higher-education/</guid>
      <description>From the WordPress in Education Panel at WordCamp Boston 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to Love Documentation</title>
      <link>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/learn-to-love-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.lastletterdesign.com/learn-to-love-documentation/</guid>
      <description>From the teaser:
You don’t know it yet, but documentation is actually AMAZING. Channel your inner educator and get inspired! We’ll talk about the different ways developers and end users try to solve problems, where they look to find information, and how you can get ahead of those needs by putting your recommendations in those places. Documentation is an amazing and complex problem that doesn’t end at a wiki full of pages—so let’s talk about how we can use our UI, different ways of phrasing and explaining, and the features we have available in WordPress to be the best teachers we can be.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>